<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raja Simon</title>
    <link>https://rajasimon.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Raja Simon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 11:22:32 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rajasimon.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Populate Database Fields</title>
      <link>https://rajasimon.io/auto-populates-database-fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 11:22:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajasimon.io/auto-populates-database-fields/</guid>
      <description>Few years back I&amp;rsquo;ve created many open source projects and we have seen the successfull one beatserer in my previous blog although there is another repository lying in Github and I really really thought it was cool so here I&amp;rsquo;m telling you all about that hoping you will like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to run periodic background task using Django Channels</title>
      <link>https://rajasimon.io/django-channels-background-task/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 21:20:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajasimon.io/django-channels-background-task/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to run Django background task with Django Channels. I&amp;rsquo;ve created the beatserver python package for those who wanted to run background task inside the Django server without using external dependencies. Well, Channel itself another dependency but soon it will merge in to Django so I say now you need just Channels as the first dependecies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Project Structure Best Practices 2020</title>
      <link>https://rajasimon.io/django-project-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 12:56:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajasimon.io/django-project-structure/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;m writing about how to create the best folder structure for your Django application. Django folder structure is consist of project and apps. If you are not creating the right folder structure at the beginning of the project, everything looks enormous and complex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create Django Multi-Page Application</title>
      <link>https://rajasimon.io/django-multi-page-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 12:56:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajasimon.io/django-multi-page-application/</guid>
      <description>We all know about single-page applications, but what is this multi-page application and how that is different from monolith architecture. And does we call serverless architecture a multi-page application?. In this post, we are going to see what it is and what are the benefit of using it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Google Analytics for development</title>
      <link>https://rajasimon.io/stop-google-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 17:25:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajasimon.io/stop-google-analytics/</guid>
      <description>For every project that I’ve set up Google Analytics, I wish Google automatically detects when I’m in local development and completely turn off analytics. For some environment, you can’t exclude the local environment just by using IP and ISP. You just need some solid way to detect you’re in the local environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Blog Post</title>
      <link>https://rajasimon.io/first-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 11:19:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajasimon.io/first-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m starting this blog post to try Hugo static site generator and stumbled upon how incredible fast is this. Fast, meaning it&amp;rsquo;s fast. So let&amp;rsquo;s write a few more blog posts for a few days and figure out what sticks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>